The world is in chaos.
How many people
will be displaced
and lose their loved ones?
The pain of losing loved ones...
We both know it well.
What's more,
when a nest is overturned,
no egg remains intact.
I finally understand the meaning behind Lady Zhao's music.
Thank you, Lady Zhao.
Xiaolian,
having a brother like you
is truly wonderful.
I also wish Lady Zhao all the best.
Thank you.
Wine.
Why did you protect me tonight?
Didn't you say
you wanted me to protect you?
I was just saying that.
You don't have to take it seriously.
Don't take it seriously.
Anyway,
you don't have to do this.
Oh.
You said
you would take me back
to a good life in broad daylight.
Yeah.
I did say that.
Xiaolian.
Uncle.
Xiaolian is awake.
Brother.
Are you feeling
a little better today?
Much better.
Brother,
where are we?
Aren't we at home?
This is someone else's house.
We'll go home tonight.
Brother,
is the Lantern Festival coming soon?
Today is the Lantern Festival.
The Lantern Festival.
Then brother,
can I go see the lanterns
for the Lantern Festival?
Do you really want to see the lanterns?
Of course.
Isn't the Lantern Festival all about seeing lanterns?
Then tonight I will hang lanterns all over the courtyard.
We can watch the lanterns at home.
How does that sound?
Great!
I can see the lanterns too!
Hey.
Sir,
stand firm.
This Sister Zhao
looks very familiar.
But she doesn't smile.
Is it because my brother's story is boring?
You know my story is boring too.
You like to smile,
how can you make others smile with you?
Please don't mind her, Lady Zhao.
My sister and I
are used to joking around.
It's fine.
I also felt
Xiaolian looked familiar just now.
I zoned out
for a moment.
You look so pretty when you smile, Sister.
You have the most beautiful smile Xiaolian has ever seen.
You must smile more, Sister,
smile more,
then you won't be in so much pain.
You can tell
that I have an illness?
Of course.
We are the same kind of people.
So you should smile more,
okay?
Meng.
Have you seen the Chief come back?
Not yet.
What's wrong?
The Chief insisted on going to catch the suspect alone,
and wouldn't let me follow.
It's been over two hours,
and they still haven't returned.
I am truly worried.
Oh.
You have a daughter
who went missing when she was five.
You have been looking for her for over a decade.
Now,
she should be around Lord Chu's age.
Sir,
does your daughter
have any distinguishing marks?
My daughter
has a
pink plum blossom birthmark on her thigh.
Sir.
Are you sure she has a pink plum blossom birthmark on her leg?
I am sure.
She has a pink birthmark.
Sister.
Sister,
how did it go?
Cui Hong is taken care of.
According to the original plan,
in half an hour,
we should leave for Wuyou City.
Where is the Daoist priest?
Everything is ready.
They are waiting for orders in the guest room.
Have you been overthinking these past two days,
and tired yourself out again?
I just tried a new medicine.
Maybe
my body hasn't adapted to it yet.
New medicine?
Did you find a new method?
Yes.
That's great.
That's really great.
Sister,
is it time to leave?
It's just that
Liang Shicheng's personal letter hasn't arrived yet.
Could something have happened?
You're probably overthinking it, sister.
It should
just be delayed by an hour or two.
It's fine.
We caught Cui Hong today.
He said
Liang Shicheng and Chancellor Cai were fighting behind the scenes,
which is why they wouldn't let me go.
If the two of them noticed something,
then it would be extremely dangerous.
Don't worry, sister.
There's still time.
If this doesn't work,
we'll try another way.
I'm just afraid there are no other ways.
There is one,
but
it's much more dangerous.